http://www.steelking.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.steelking.com and Steel King Industries, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Steel King Industries, Inc. include www.steelking.com and Steel King. The Steel King website is a product and service information site. By using the Steel King website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
Steel King does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Steel King may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Steel King, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Steel King may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Steel King or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Steel King; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Steel King, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
Steel King may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Steel King, in order to determine what Steel King services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Steel King to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Steel King. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Steel King website.
Use of Cookies
The Steel King website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Steel King pages, or register with Steel King site or services, a cookie helps Steel King to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Steel King website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Steel King features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Steel King services or websites you visit.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Security of your Personal Information
Steel King secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Steel King uses the following methods for this purpose:
–          SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
Steel King does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, Steel King may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Steel King or click on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Steel King, you may opt out of such communications by managing communications on the Subscription page.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this Statement
Steel King reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
Steel King welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Steel King has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Steel King at:
Steel King Industries, Inc.
2700 Chamber St.
Stevens Point, Wisconsin 54481
Email Address:
info@steelking.com
Telephone number:
715-341-3120
Effective as of July 1, 2019
Request a Quote
Latest News
MHEDA’s 2020 Women in Industry event goes all-virtual
This past week dozens of women for gathered – virtually – for MHEDA’s first...
Read Article
MHEDA’s 2021 MVS Award
Steek King® has been awarded MHEDA’s Most Valuable Supplier designation for 2021, based on...
Read Article
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are as essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
